landingi.com 2015-02-20

# Privacy policy - Landingi

This Privacy Policy is intended to provide a sense of security to each user of the [www.landingi.com](http://www.landingi.com/) website. The use of our website constitutes acceptance of the Privacy Policy.

**I. Administrator**

The data administrator is Landingi Sp. z o.o. based in Krakow, ul. Ludwinowska 7/9, entered in the Register of Entrepreneurs under KRS number 0000449404, for which registration documents are held by the District Court for Krakow-Srodmiescie in the city of Krakow, 11th Commercial Division of the National Court Register, NIP (tax id): 6762461659, REGON (statistical no.): 122774425. Data protection is ensured in accordance with the requirements of generally applicable laws, and data are stored on secure servers.

**II. Cookies**

The www.landingi.com site uses cookies. They are 16 text files sent by a web server and stored by computer browser software. When the browser reconnects to the site, the site recognizes the type of device used by the user for connecting. Parameters allow to read the information contained in the cookies only to the server that created them. Therefore cookies make it easier to use the previously visited sites.

The information collected relate to the IP address, the type of browser used, language, operating system type, internet service provider, information about the time and date, location, and information sent to the site via a contact form.

**III. Advantages of cookies**

The collected data are used to monitor and determine how users use our websites, to improve functioning of the service in order to ensure more efficient and seamless navigation. Monitoring of information about users is performed with use of the Google Analitics tool that registers user behaviour on a site.

Cookies identify the user, allowing to adjust the content of the website to user’s needs. Remembering user preferences allows for proper fit of displayed advertisements. We use cookies to ensure the highest comfort standard of our site, and the collected data are used by Landingi Sp. z o.o. only internally in order to optimize activities.

**IV. Security of data**

The data are stored and processed in accordance with the Polish law. We respect the privacy of our users, therefore the stored data are confidential and not shared with third parties. Their security is a high priority for us, that is why they are collected on safe and protected servers.

Cookies can not access data on the user's disk, nor are able to establish user’s identity. Either they do not track user’s activities after leaving our site.

**V. Types of cookies used**

On our site we use the following types of cookies:

a) "essential" cookies which allow to use the services available on the website, such as authentication cookies used for services that require authentication through the website;

b) cookies used to ensure safety, such as the ones used for detection of fraud in authentication through the website;

c) "performance" cookies for collecting information about use of the website;

d) "functional" cookies for "saving" user-selected settings and customizing the user interface, as regards for example language or region of origin of the user, font size, website appearance etc.;

e) "advertising" cookies that allow to provide users with advertising content more tailored to their interests.

**VI. Cookie management**

Users can at any time disable or enable the option of cookies collection by modifying the settings in their browser. Instruction for cookie management is available at http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/.

Additional personal information, such as e-mail address, are collected only in places where the user expressly consents thereto while completing a form. These data are stored and used by us only for purposes necessary to perform a particular function.

**VII. Final Provisions**

This document is only valid on the [www.landingi.com](http://www.landingi.com/) website. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on other sites, including the sites referred to by links contained on www.landingi.com. In case of using other websites, please read the privacy policy and cookie policy as determined by those websites.

We reserve the right to make changes to the Privacy Policy by appropriate modification of the foregoing. Any changes will not, however, undermine the basic principles of the safety and security of user data.
